I got 50% more than last time.
Pay me at least $50.
Pyongsong, Pyongan Province
Watch it, kid!
Put your hands up!
Get back!
I didn't steal it.
It's my prescription drug.
He knows that.
Tell him.
How are you feeling?
Director?
- Leave us.
- Yes, sir.
KIM Du-won and PARK Gwang-dong
are up to something.
LEE Tae-Han, director of
the Reconnaissance General Bureau
(director a North Korean CIA)
We dug around them.
They're secretly selling us out
to the Chinese.
They're working with RYU In-chin
of State Security.
What do you think
they're planning?
Is it a coup?
But the traitors are blocking
access to the top.
I can't report to
our Great General myself.
They must be killed,
so I can report to him.
Why me and not the elite unit?
Think.
PARK has the Supreme Guard Command.
KIM has the State Security troops.
If one of our agents fails
in striking them, it'll be war.
Isn't it obvious?
But you left us a long time ago.
Comrade Cheol-woo.
Comrade UHM.
After this mission,
your family will be named heroes
who saved the country from a coup.
You have my word.
SEOUL
- Thank you.
- The voter turnout is 75. 9%.
80.3%, the election results
are coming in.
I'm sorry.
With all the child support
I give your mom,
doesn't she feed you?
- She won't let us eat junk food.
- Then eat lots.
- Dad.
- Yeah?
Can't you and Mom
get back together?
Tell me a good reason
why we should.
Mom's a doctor
and you're at the Blue House.
I lost my super cool
when you two got divorced.
- Super cool?
- Yup.
Se-min?
Do your friends ever mention
that you're rude?
Yup.
- They do?
- Yup.
You're definitely my son.
Hold on. Wait.
We have to go at 6:00.
Mom's coming.
Okay.
EXIT POLL RESULTS
Sir! Congratulations!
Well, it's close.
But all the stations
predict the same results.
Se-rim! Se-min!
Had fun with dad?
What? You ate hamburgers?
A lecture?
I'm filling in?
Of course, I'll do it.
I'm an expert at filling in, right?
Yes, sir.
Right.
I'll see you then.
Take care.
Where'd they go?
PYONGYANG
STEEL RAIN
TOGETHER FOR UNITY
The guest is here for Room 1.
Hello.
I heard your boss is troubled over
the Kaesong Industrial Complex.
Yes.
He'll express his position
to Foreign Affairs tomorrow.
Chinese companies opening at Kaesong
goes against UN sanctions to...
No way.
Making household goods is okay.
They'll come to the six-party talks
with the next administration here.
We should give them something.
We must give and take
with North Korea.
KIM Du-won?
The minister of State Security?
Did No. 1 kill him?
I don't think it's his doing.
Chief of Chinese State Security
to South Korea, LEE Hong-jang
Officially, it was a car accident.
- Who is this man?
- RYU In-chin.
Chief of Chinese State Security
to North Korea.
The last intelligence
he gave me was that
there will be massive purges
in North Korea.
The next administration
has its work cut out.
What will you do
when you leave the Blue House?
Faculty chair at Peking University's
East Asian Research Center?
Interested?
Like seafood stir-fry, sir?
Yes.
They make the best stir-fry here.
- A medium seafood stir-fry.
- Yes.
Make that a large, please.
There will be massive purges
in North Korea.
The struggle for power there
has gotten serious, sir.
Officially, North Korea and China
say it was a car accident.
Should we inform
the President-elect?
PRESIDENT-ELECT KIM KYUNG-YOUNG
He'll find out eventually.
It's more fun that way, right?
Right.
Yes, sir.
Another customer.
I know. Serve that table.
- What would you like?
- Skinny noodles, please.
I'll be right back.
PARK at Kaesong on 24th.
Press 1 to call me.
What was the start of
20th century Korea?
- The Japan-Korea Treaty of 1910.
- Yes.
But we call it
the National humiliation year.
The 36 years of Japanese rule
ended in 1945.
But let's point out something here.
Germany, which started
the war in Europe,
was divided into East and West.
But in Asia,
Korea got cut in half, not Japan.
Did we start the war?
We couldn't get independence
on our own.
Right.
Then what happened?
- The Korean War.
- Yes.
The first Cold War proxy war
broke out on our land.
Our people were taken away
to slavery and wars, then died.
Including the comfort women,
3 million people died.
Another 3 million died
in the Korean War.
20 to 25% of the population
were killed.
It means
1 out of 4 or 5 of you died.
In the 20th century, our ideology
was based on Japan.
So what did we do?
We followed Japan
in Japanese style.
The result?
Samsung beats Sony
and Hyundai outsells Honda.
That's how we took action against
this ideology called Japan.
Then what about North Korea?
How was Japan defeated?
Nuclear bombs.
Nukes!
Nuclear weapons!
North Korea will be defeated
with nukes just like Japan!
What?
What kind of bullshit is that?
Huh?
I'm right, aren't I?
Nukes can only be stopped
by nukes!
Everyone knows that!
Think about it.
Professor JUNG Se-Yong
Head of Presidential Transition Team
If we have nukes,
it won't be this complicated.
Or have the nuclear option
like the Japanese.
If not that,
declare to review having nukes.
- Strengthen our position first!
- Taxi!
- Get in there.
- Come on!
You're drunk. Go home.
- Just one more drink?
- No! Go home.
Please?
Just one more drink?
- Please?
- Why you!
- Merry Christmas!
- Merry Christmas boys!
- Hello! Happy Christmas!
- Come on.
They greeted us.
I'll pay.
Just one more drink?
I have an early meeting tomorrow.
I gotta go.
Take care!
- Go home!
- Come on!
Go home safely.
Just one more drink, please?
Eat up, In-young.
You're pretty and sweet.
And you're very smart in school.
Don't listen to South Korean music
and you'll be fine.
Dad?
Have you heard of G-Dragon?
G-dragon?
He's a famous musician not just
in the South, but the whole world.
The Chinese and Russians
listen to his music too.
Why you!
You want to ruin your life?
Listening to South Korean music
could have us killed!
Say you won't listen to it.
I said the Chinese and Russians
listen to it, not me.
I won't listen to it.
Hurry up and eat.
What is this?
I've received a mission again.
You'll be sent to
the embassy in Cuba.
Take this money.
Cuba? What do you mean?
It's a hard opportunity to get.
Go ahead without me.
I'm not sure what this is,
but I'm not going until you return.
It'll take long.
I'll join you later.
Take In-young and go first.
Cheol-woo! Cheol-woo!
In-young wants to say goodbye.
Daddy?
Have a safe trip.
It's cold, dear.
In-young must be cold.
Go inside.
KAESONG INDUSTRIAL COMPLEX
COMRADE KIM DU-WON
PARK GWANG-DONG
CHIEF OF SUPREME GUARD COMMAND
Move out.
NORTHERN GYEONGGI-DO
Our leader is headed for Kaesong.
And Park mobilized
the supreme guard command.
Where's Park now?
In Pyongyang, sir.
Get the helicopter!
Then he...
Yes, that's right!
PARK! That bastard!
Oh, please.
They're trying to be up front
to get noticed.
Move! Go back!
Our Supreme Leader has arrived!
General!
Long live our Great General!
This is overload,
requesting search for one MLRS.
Requesting search for
Indian zero niner. Over.
Wilco.
PARK Gwang-dong...
What is it?
MINISTER OF PEOPLE'S ARMED FORCES
CHIEF OF THE GENERAL STAFF OF
THE KOREAN PEOPLE'S ARMY
DIRECTOR OF
THE GENERAL POLITICAL BUREAU
we've got the Orphan located.
Will attempt communication.
No. 1 here, but no sign of PARK.
SENDING
FAILED TO SEND
Red alert! MLRS is active
and has fired a rocket.
General!
Acknowledge a go for engaging fire
on MLRS. Overload actual?
Confirm?
You all right?
Hang in there.
It's another one!
Look!
Everyone run!
The Americans did this.
Understood?
Leave no survivors!
South Korea's 20 minutes away!
It's a coup!
I can't stay here!
Call Ministry of Foreign Affairs!
I want out of here!
Look!
It's our Great General!
Su-mi! Wait!
Help us!
Help!
That way!
Get the truck!
Look!
His leg!
Oh no! It's terrible!
Tie this around it.
Loosen his clothing.
What if he can't breathe?
I'm sorry, sir.
Our General's hand is so cold!
General!
We'll shut down the oil pipelines!
It'll be your fault!
It'll be your fault.
Talk to your leadership.
CHINESE AMBASSADOR
TO NORTH KOREA
Yes, sir.
Open it now!
Open the gates!
Get in your cars!
Hurry!
Close the gates!
Close the gates now!
Go close the gates now!
Are you insane?
That's to South Korea!
We can't go back up now!
Get down!
It's pine mushroom tea.
The guest should be served first.
She must be nervous
before the new homeowner.
But I'm still the owner, right?
Enjoy.
Let's see...
Was this your third elections?
My second presidential elections.
Oh, that's right.
I must tell you.
Since I became president,
I'm the happiest now.
No matter what you do here,
people blame you.
No one's pointing fingers
at me now.
What is it?
An MLRS from the US Army
2nd Division went missing at dawn.
The seized MLRS just fired
2 Steel Rain bombs at Kaesong.
The ROK-US Combined Forces
request issuance of DEFCON 3.
Who seized the MLRS?
Bodies found at the scene
were in our military attire,
but their tags were fake.
We'll investigate, but...
Wait.
Hold on.
Isn't today the opening day
for Chinese companies at Kaesong?
Excuse me.
- It's urgent.
- What is it?
Chinese Foreign Ministry requested
entry for their people from Kaesong.
- It's an emergency.
- Let them in.
We should help.
Let them through!
This is Kwak.
We shouldn't meet?
Our Leader was killed
in the Kaesong bombing!
The civil war here
should be dealt with first.
The nuclear weapons
and Pyongyang...
I have full command of them.
Is China with me or not?
How could you leak it to the press
without consulting us first?
We've still got a few months left.
Goodbye, Walter.
Joanne Martin
CIA Station Chief in South Korea
Come now, Mr. Kwak.
U.S military weapons were used here,
in South Korea,
to launch an attack
on North Korea.
That puts us in the cross hairs.
We needed to clear our name.
Now,
we're convinced that a coup
has broken out in the North.
I've managed to quiet
the press for a while, but
word around town is that
No. 1 is dead.
All wars begin with propaganda.
Mr. Kwak.
Have a good evening.
Mr. Lee?
Doctor! Help!
Hurry!
We're closed for today.
Excuse me!
You can't go in there!
We don't deliver babies here.
Look.
I'm a gynecologist.
I'll call an ambulance.
Treat him.
I promise I won't hurt you.
I'm a gynecologist.
Please go somewhere else.
I won't report this.
Still, you're a doctor!
Please treat him. Hurry!
Please, doctor.
Isn't that...
don't call our General that!
General!
What's your blood type?
Su-mi?
Your blood is going into
our Great General now?
I hope it's good enough
for our Great General.
What an honor!
Director? It's Cheol-woo.
PARK didn't come,
but our Leader did.
Then we got attacked.
What happened?
PARK acted too fast.
Where are you, comrade?
Il-San, sir.
Il-San? In the South?
Yes, sir.
I'm with the Great General.
How is his status?
He's alive, but critical.
Listen carefully.
We must bring back
his corpse at least.
When PARK realizes he is dead,
the coup will be successful.
Stay there and protect him.
I'll send people soon.
Yes, sir.
These tanks are from
Sariwon 815 Mechanized Corps.
These are from the 820 Armored Corps
of Pyongyang Defense Command.
The 815 tanks retreated back
after the battle.
The 820 Armored Corps remain
defending Pyongyang to the south.
It's a coup, sir.
Find out who's behind it
and if it succeeded or not.
Yes, sir.
Sir?
It's not confirmed yet,
but during the bombing
North Korea's No. 1
may have died.
- And...
- And what?
Wait.
North Korea may declare war.
What!
Though we're in transition,
a secretary can't barge into
a ministerial meeting like this!
Who's your source of intelligence?
The CIA and
the Chinese State Security, sir.
I did what I could.
He got shot
in the head, shoulder, and thigh.
I patched the hole
in his shoulder.
I took out the one
in the thigh.
There's femoral artery rupture,
but I could only bandage it.
The biggest problem
is the one in the cranial cavity.
But I can't do it.
Why not?
You're a doctor.
I'm not a neurosurgeon.
Unless it's a baby inside here,
there's nothing I can do.
My people are coming.
Please treat him till then.
North Korea's...
President is here!
I mean... Geeze!
What are you doing in the dark?
Looking for some food.
You keep food here?
Yes, it's up here.
It's hot.
Here. Try it.
Isn't this yi-bap?
What?
This is yi-bap.
You know, rice.
Right.
It's white rice.
Can we eat this black thing?
It's really good!
It's meat!
After getting paid today,
I was going to exchange it for food.
There's no food at home.
My family must be starving.
LYEO Min-KYUNG!
They'll be resting comfortably
at home.
They should worry about you.
Eat up.
We have to protect
our Great General, right?
Eat.
And stop crying.
Try the black stuff.
It's sweet and yummy.
She made it so easily too.
- Stay inside the room.
- Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Where's our Leader?
Drop the gun.
Move.
Hold tight!
Su-mi! Look!
The General is bleeding!
I think it's my blood.
Su-mi!
Lay her down, quickly!
No!
You have to focus!
Press down hard.
She has to get surgery.
She lost too much blood!
- Su-mi! Wake up!
- There's no time!
We can't.
Find a place
to treat her in secret.
Please save Su-mi.
Su-mi! Wake up!
Su-hyeon? I need your help.
This way! Hurry!
- Sook-Jung?
- This way!
What's going on?
Take them to the emergency!
I'm a plastic surgeon!
I'm a gynecologist!
At least you're a surgeon.
Move.
Go in here. This way!
Hey!
What's going on?
Help us.
I won't hurt you.
Please Su-hyeon...
First, let's save them.
Let's save her first.
NARCOTIC DRUGS
What are you doing?
Why aren't you treating her?
Doctor!
Su-mi! No!
No! You can't die!
Su-mi!
Sir!
The report came in
from the scene at Il-San.
I'm listening.
Three bodies presumed to be
North Korean operatives were found.
A Chinese van full of panda dolls
from Kaesong was also there.
North Korean operatives?
A 911 call was made from there
20 minutes before the shootings.
About what?
Saying the North Korean president
was there.
What? Give me that.
North Korea doesn't have
a president.
KWON Sook-Jung.
Gynecologist?
NASTY WOMAN
Se-rim? It's daddy.
Is your mom home?
With Aunt Sook-Jung?
She's still at work?
It's nothing.
Go back to bed.
I'll be at this address.
Call me an hour later.
If I don't pick up,
send the police.
No!
Send special forces!
Got that?
What? Why?
In one hour! don't forget!
What's going on, sir?
- Call me in an hour!
- Sir!
I heard North Korea was beyond
the river by Jayu-ro Highway.
But I guess it didn't
really hit me.
It's so close by...
I'm sorry.
Su-hyeon!
Why don't you ever
answer your phone?
What the?
- Cheol-woo!
- It's okay, Su-hyeon.
Get all their hand phones.
I'm so sorry.
- I'm so sorry for this.
- It's okay.
Get things to tie them with!
Sit!
Sit down!
That man over there
is your No. 1, right?
A coup occurred there,
so you couldn't go back.
You snuck in
when the Chinese came, right?
Who are you?
Some coincidence this is.
Maybe it's more like fate.
I'm head secretary of
National Security.
I work for the No. 1 here.
I'll help you.
No matter how skilled you are,
what can you do
with just that one girl?
Let's say we help
your No. 1 to recover.
Then what?
How will you take him back?
You rotten bastard!
The men who tried to kill
No. 1 at Il-San
are your people.
Our help is your best bet now.
Act wisely.
Shut up!
North Korea will soon declare war.
We declare war against
the U.S. and South Korea!
American imperialists and
South Koreans puppets
dared to take aim yesterday
at our Dear Leader
and top commanding officers
by bombarding Kaesong.
Upon this unpardonable atrocity,
the Supreme Command
terminates the armistice agreement
and declares war.
If they pull anything,
kill them.
Once war breaks out,
our mighty army
will burn down the mutts
of the U.S. and the Blue House
with nuclear bombs!
I'll declare martial law.
Get ready.
How is our Leader?
If he doesn't get surgery now,
he could die.
But why the declaration of war?
Who's in control of Pyongyang?
PARK Gwang-dong!
It was the only way to stop him
from bringing in the frontline troops.
This phone is tapped.
We got attacked at Il-San
and almost died.
I think...
we should request help
from the South.
It's the only way
to save our Leader.
Comrade Cheol-woo!
Watch for your phone
being tapped, sir.
The declaration of war is a show.
It's because of PARK Gwang-dong
staging the coup!
It was to stop PARK from
mobilizing the frontline troops.
The South must not act recklessly
and just wait!
Stay still, when they declared war?
That's crazy!
Save our Leader as promised.
Let our frontline troops
go to Pyongyang
to stop the coup.
Convince your government
to help us.
It's the only way
to save the Korean Peninsula.
B-52 from the mainland will
deploy these missiles.
Nuclear-tipped cruise missiles will strike
the Pyongyang Defense Command,
as well as frontline troops,
military installations near the DMZ
that are a direct threat to
South Korea.
This will permanently demilitarize
the North Korean army.
A nuclear strike on the North
will cause immense damage
from EMP and radiation.
Yes, Maybe.
Maybe there could be some damage.
But a full-scale conventional war
with the North Korea will result in
over three hundred thousand
casualties at best,
which can easily escalate to
roughly 2. 5 million.
Our simulation calculates the cost of war
at 1 trillion U.S. dollars,
and an additional 3 trillion
in post-war restorations.
And this is only in the case that
North Korea does not use nuclear weapons.
If they use their
nuclear weapons, well,
our simulation would be meaningless.
Should the ROK-U.S.
Combined Forces Command succeed,
we project zero casualties
at a total cost of three hundred billion
dollars up to the point of full stabilization.
If the South Korean government agrees to cover
two hundred and 50 billion of those costs,
the U.S. will compensate
the remaining 50 billion.
If it's unavoidable,
I'll agree to war.
But it should be the last resort
after exploring all options.
And a nuclear war is...
we are merely proposing these revisions in
a response to the South Korean government's
request to activate
Operation Plan 5027.
That's right.
We requested this meeting.
I appreciate your cordial review
and suggestions.
Without hindering the operation,
could you tell us
how much time we have?
Our simulation tells us that
North Korea will require
forty-eight hours in preparation for war.
B-52 will leave from
Minot Air Force Base in North Dakota.
Mission time to point of target
will approximate twelve hours,
which means you have at most thirty-six
hours from now to reach a decision.
President Lee,
this will all occur during
your presidential term.
North Korea's No. 1 is here.
I have him. He is unconscious.
As the President of
the Republic of Korea,
- I order the preemptive nuclear...
- Sir!
Sir!
These were at the scene.
The uniform and chocolate
were found in the van.
- Keep that separate.
- Yes, sir.
All clear.
No threat of danger.
- Send this to digital forensics.
- Yes, sir.
Beloved citizens.
Article 77 of our Constitution...
and Articles 2 and 10
of the Martial Law Act,
as of 6:00 AM on December 25th,
I declare the nation
under martial law.
Beloved citizens,
please go on with
your daily lives.
I ask that you cooperate
with us and the militarized command.
So?
The polygraph shows
that he's telling the truth.
And the girl?
She doesn't know anything, sir.
My, my.
You surprised me with this one.
You went to your wife
during a national crisis,
and captured the enemy head.
Not bad for a substitute.
Good work.
Amazing!
Thank you, sir.
He can't see us, right?
Right.
He has something to say.
To me?
How's our Leader's condition?
I reported
that your government is helping.
If anything happens to him,
it's all your country's fault!
You folks started the mess!
Why is it all our fault?
Man.
The first round is over,
so rest up.
If anything happens to him,
it'll be war!
Okay!
While you were bringing in No. 1,
Chief Park of National Security
let out that we had No. 1.
- They responded right away.
- Who?
North Korea will come
to check and talk.
We almost agreed to
a preemptive nuclear strike.
The President-elect said to meet
the North Korean rep, then decide.
We stopped the war for now.
Who's coming down?
And who's going to meet him?
Well...
We suggested meeting first,
but they won't give us any info.
The Blue House insists on
sending someone.
They want all the credit.
Chief Park's ambitions are too high.
Hello, sir.
What's he up to?
- Just sleeping, sir.
- Did he eat?
No, he won't eat.
It's me.
I bought you a hamburger.
Know what this is?
What do they call it
in North Korea?
Bread with meat?
Try a taste of capitalism?
The report said
your name is UHM Cheol-woo.
We must be destined to meet.
My name's KWAK Cheol-woo.
What does your name mean?
Mine means 'bright world'.
Born in 1977?
I'm a year older than you.
Show some respect
when I'm talking to you.
What's wrong?
Call a doctor! Now!
It's okay.
Just give me painkillers.
Take all that.
But let's give him this.
Yes, sir.
Here.
Let's stop your drug addiction
while you're down here.
You're a young man
with many years left to live.
You must be cold.
Want the hamburger?
So?
They'll come by tunnels
in secret.
Tunnels?
Our country dug up
20 tunnels in the last 60 years.
I heard a handful
can reach here.
Tunnels, huh?
Who's coming down?
The RGB controls the tunnels.
Only our director
can open them in emergencies.
You mean director LEE Tae-Han?
Wait.
He's a known hardliner on us.
Would he come down
to stop the war?
Such dichotomy won't do any good.
Why not just kill him when he comes
and start the war?
Calm down, pal.
You're sure LEE Tae-Han is coming?
If our Leader recovers,
PARK's coup is ruined.
LEE will come
to make sure of that.
Take me to the meeting.
I'll explain to him.
He's close enough to LEE Tae-Han
to report directly to him, sir.
- If we go with him...
- LEE Tae-Han?
Director LEE Tae-Han of the RGB?
Yes, sir.
Then LEE will trust us.
It'll speed up the talks.
We don't work with red guerrilla.
What do you mean, sir?
He snuck in and used weapons.
That makes him a guerilla.
That guerrilla saved your ass.
What the hell!
Sorry, sir.
I thought you hung up.
This red dot is the GPS signal
of Chief Park's car.
Just follow the signal, sir.
They agreed to send our Leader back
once he recovers, right?
Probably.
Unless he wants to defect to here.
How dare you say that?
Where is our Leader now?
At a safe place.
But he's probably not doing
so hot from the gun shots.
Think this is funny?
Why do you always joke around?
If he dies and they blame you,
we'll be forced to go to war.
Think you'll be joking then?
I know, I know.
I know it'll be war
if your No. 1 dies.
I have two kids.
Would I lie to you?
They can't operate
until his brain pressure goes down.
Hold on.
What's he doing?
Why stop here at Uijeongbu?
Aren't they coming by tunnel?
You folks dug to here?
I don't know the exact locations.
Do you eat moles up there?
No way!
We eat rice with meat.
If you don't eat moles,
how can you dig so well?
When we're reunified,
you dig the subway lines.
Must be around here...
You folks made lots of army bases
to prepare for war.
So many army base pubs here.
Look, pal.
Those aren't army base pubs.
During the time of our dad's uncles,
the army base stew was made.
With some food from
American army bases.
The Americans made the bases?
Just forget it.
I don't believe it.
At a critical time like this?
They came here to eat.
Aren't you hungry, pal?
Forget it.
Let's eat too.
We need the energy
to interrupt their meeting.
One of my favorite restaurants
is nearby here.
Come on. It's just over there.
I haven't had this in a while.
Why?
Eat it.
Give me your hand.
We're a team, right?
We're working together.
Move over.
Ma'am? Another bowl, please!
And some dumplings too.
Dang.
You eat well.
I didn't eat since Kaesong.
And
you shoved the ham bread thing
in your mouth, remember?
Eat all you want.
Eat up.
I like skinny noodles.
What's that?
We ordered dumplings too.
They're called skinny noodles.
Are you a defector too?
He came down here recently.
Where are all the customers?
They left because
it's close to the North?
Aren't you heading south?
If there's a war,
all of Korea won't be safe.
I'm worried about my family
up there more than me.
I'll unlock it.
No funny business, okay?
I'll do it.
Hey! Wait for me!
My scarf!
My wife gave me that.
Got a wife and kids?
You left that information blank.
I have a 13 year-old girl
and a 10 year-old boy.
And you saw my ex-wife.
Why'd you divorce the doctor?
Dang.
Let's not talk about that.
How about some music?
I have a wife
and an 8 year-old girl.
Do you know G-dragon,
the singer?
Of course.
If you don't, you'd be a spy.
Did you come before as a spy?
My daughter likes him.
He's popular with the girls.
My daughter always plays his songs.
That's him. Listen.
This is world-class music?
Your daughter said that?
Then accept it.
My daughter always wins too.
Forget the candy-coated comfort
Tonight, I'll be crooked
Leave me alone
I was alone anyway
There is no reason
There is no sincerity
Is that LEE Tae-Han?
Take a look.
I can't really tell.
I can't see from here.
Call LEE and tell him
we're close by.
We can go if LEE lets us,
or else Chief PARK will be fuming!
I can't see.
Is that him?
What?
What was that?
- Snipers!
- What?
Calm down.
Stay calm.
Rocket launcher!
I'm at the Nodongdangsa!
Send troops here now!
Get in!
Hurry!
Go after them.
Take it!
I trust you.
Now!
Director!
Chief!
Who are you?
- Who...
- Comrade Cheol-woo.
After this mission,
your family will be named heroes
for saving the country from a coup.
What the hell!
Are you out of your mind!
It's the only way to stop the war!
Why's that commie here!
What the hell did you do!
Freeze! Don't move!
I'm secretary KWAK Cheol-woo
of National Security.
Call an ambulance!
You're saying,
PARK Gwang-dong, who raised the coup,
is dead, so the situation is over?
The operative who brought
No. 1 down said that?
Yes, sir.
Where is he now?
He's hurt and unconscious.
He's being treated now.
Explain this.
Chief Park had this recorded
before he died.
How's our Leader?
He's being treated.
What's the situation there?
Military traitors staged a coup.
But I have control of Pyongyang
and the nuclear weapons.
Don't worry.
If our Leader is repatriated,
I'll take out the traitors
and retract the declaration...
They're always like this!
They said they wanted to talk,
then sunk the Cheonan!
Then they attacked
Yeonpyeong Island!
Only two things are certain now!
They declared war
and have nuclear weapons!
There is one more, sir.
We have the North Korean leader.
One more thing.
People in North Korea
are trying hard to stop the war too.
Rather than trust them,
I'll consult with our allies.
You mean you'll issue
the preemptive attack?
Will you bet the lives of our people
on something with a 50% probability?
The cost of war and
rebuilding North Korea aside,
they'll never see us as compatriots
if we attack with nuclear bombs!
Will you all excuse us?
Let's be honest now.
There's a coup in the North.
If we attack now,
they can't fight back.
We never had a chance this good
to eliminate the threat of war here!
If we miss this chance,
we'd be doing injustice to Korea.
Before I step down,
let me give a gift to you
and our country.
This time, let's do as I say.
Our economy and population rates
are all going down.
Simply put?
The country is going bust!
If you don't understand
why a divided nation must be unified,
then see reunification
as means for profit.
I disagree with a preemptive
nuclear strike.
Good thing...
The law still allows me
to decide that.
No, it's a pity.
That someone with no respect
for history is still in rule.
- Secretary Kwak?
- Yes?
- You're Mr. UHM Cheol-woo's guardian?
- Yes.
We've discovered
he has metastatic lung cancer.
He also has stage 4
pancreatic cancer.
It spread to his spine.
He could get neurogenic shock too.
He could die any minute.
Do you think he's aware of
his condition?
He has to know.
He'd be in extreme pain.
You're up?
How do you feel?
Good.
I slept well for a change.
The bullet wound must hurt.
With all the painkillers,
I don't feel it.
That's good.
I'm glad, but...
Why'd you kill PARK Gwang-dong?
That's the order I received.
PARK raised the coup,
so kill him.
That's the reason?
Don't you think it's weird?
He started the coup
and was about to take over for good.
Then why risk his life
to come down here?
What are you getting at?
Things don't add up.
Usually, coups are staged
by the military.
But President Park was killed by
the director of the KCIA.
Yes.
But the military led
the coup later.
Here too.
Mr. Lee?
Yes, sir.
I'll be back. Get some rest.
As of 6:00 am today,
the nation is under martial law.
A curfew will be in effect
from midnight to 5:00 am.
Please return home
as soon as possible.
Going somewhere, sir?
I'm returning to China.
I received orders to evacuate.
It's urgent.
Let's exchange some information.
How's No. 1?
50:50.
Who is China currently supporting
as a leader of North Korea?
We can only support
the one in control of North Korea.
So you told both the rebels
and the opposition that No. 1 is here?
I didn't, but my superiors
may have done so.
The coup was staged by
the military, right?
No. 1 killed hundreds of generals
since he came into power.
And he practically has
sole control of the nuclear weapons.
Then who could it be?
If we bomb North Korea,
will we be enemies?
What will you give me?
PARK Gwang-dong died
when he came down.
I know that.
Our president will not
expand North after the strike.
Perhaps the next president will.
After a nuclear bombing,
he won't be able to either.
The Korean race will be forced into
another new Cold War.
You're an ethnic Korean too.
So what?
Since when did Korea
treat us as brothers?
You treat the rich as brothers,
but the poor as foreigners!
Though I'm an ethnic Korean
in China,
I'm 100% Chinese.
China is firm on not sharing
our borders with the U.S.
or with countries that have
military alliances with them.
If North Korea is destroyed by war,
we'll have to take them in.
I'll tell you one last thing.
Our country doesn't like that.
If we take them in,
our forces will be dispersed.
That's what the Americans
and the Japanese want.
Good evening, Mr. Takashi.
Hello, Mr. Lee.
Are you here to depart as well?
Yes.
Shall I introduce you?
Mr. Kwak.
This is Mr. Takashi of
the Japanese CIRO.
He's an old acquaintance.
How is No. 1's status?
Fifty, fifty. (50: 50)
Thank you.
If you think of me as a brother,
take my advice.
Stop this war.
Escort Mr. Kwak home.
How about the Faculty Chair
at Peking University?
I'm Mr. Popular tonight.
Look at all the shit you must do
for splitting up a country.
I believe the president-elect
will be asking for you
within the next few hours.
When he does,
please advise him to face up
to reality.
Why should I do this?
Because you're the man that has the access
of both presidents right now, Mr. Kwak.
Face up to the reality of what?
You remember how it was
when No. 1 succeeded his father.
The North Korean government overcomes
the crisis by creating tension.
So then ask yourself,
how far would these
military authorities go
to justify their new,
illegitimate regime?
According to our simulations,
this coup will result in war.
Excuse me.
It's me. Did anything happen?
Did they decide
to strike the North?
Find out anything you can.
The Tag Heuer smart watch
you asked about...
Yes?
NIS digital forensics called, sir.
It's not just a watch.
They couldn't crack the firewall,
but it has a code generator.
A code generator?
A call from the president, sir.
WHAT BELONGS TOGETHER
WILL GROW TOGETHER
KIM KYUNG-young, speaking.
I inform you as the president.
I've agreed to a nuclear strike
on North Korea.
Mr. President!
War will break out and end
during my term.
Mr. President!
- I'll take full responsibility.
- Wait!
I understand. The South Korean president
just agreed to a nuclear attack.
You're not heading back home?
The Chinese and Japanese are
already calling their people back.
I've been told to wait it
out in Japan.
Even the U.S. isn't sure
if it can totally disarm the North.
MINOT AIR FORCE BASE
The rest of the world
is thrown in a panic,
and yet, we have time
for a cup of coffee.
This is one hell of a nation, yeah?
May I?
Oh, yeah of course.
Thank you.
It's understandable.
Back in the States,
an average of ninety people
are shot to death every day.
Yes, there's the occasional outburst
demanding tougher gun control,
but that's about it.
The next day,
the sun comes up,
another ninety lives are lost.
It's sad
when violence becomes the norm.
Whether it's to
the sound of gunshots in the U.S.
or talk of imminent war in Korea.
All I can do is just pray that
you people would eliminate
counterattack ability of the north
or that they would retract
their declaration of war.
I would put my money
on the former option, Mr. Kwak.
The best of luck to you.
PARK Gwang-dong said that
CHOI Chul-min went south, sir.
CHOI Chul-min?
He leaked our coordinates.
We should kill him!
Forget it.
Pyongyang comes first.
Once we declare ourselves as
new leaders, he's dead anyway.
Leave him.
What are you doing?
Will you shoot or not?
Damn indecisive soldier.
Got something to say?
I just did my job
to protect Pyongyang.
From whom is what matters!
Where's the detonator?
The codes?
There should be two.
Our Leader keeps the other one
on him at all times.
Retracting the war declaration
can stop the nuclear strike?
It has be retracted first
to at least try to stop it.
Give me my phone.
You got many calls.
Are they from LEE Tae-Han?
Director? It's Cheol-woo.
American nuclear bombers
are on their way.
If we retract...
Pardon?
Yes.
I'm in the hospital.
Just one guard, sir.
A watch?
What watch?
Yes, I remember.
Our Leader was wearing it.
I don't have it,
but I know where it is.
Then who should I meet and where?
Yes, sir.
Call in the hacker troops.
What did he say?
He heard from China
about the nuclear strike.
And that he'll retract
the declaration of war.
That's good.
But...
What was that about
a watch and a meeting?
Our Leader's watch...
He says to return
to the North with it.
Do you know it's a code generator
for nuclear missiles?
With all the sanctions against us...
a thought went around
in the military.
Using the nukes will kill us,
but maybe it's better than
starving to death from sanctions.
So the military devices
the last resort.
If negotiations
with nukes won't work,
then use Seoul
and the U.S. military.
What do you mean?
If we set off a nuclear rocket
over Daejeon,
all communication equipment
in the South will burn.
All their proudly advanced weapons
will become scrap metal.
Then 250,000 of our Special Forces
will seize Seoul and the U.S. army.
Then the U.S. will be forced
to negotiate.
Our military thought it was
the only way to protect ourselves.
But
when our Leader heard the plan
and didn't implement it,
some military leaders grumbled
that he intends to use the nukes
for himself and not the Republic.
There's a saying.
People of a divided nation
suffer more
from those who use
the division for political gain
than the division itself.
Wanting the watch...
It means he'll implement that plan.
How long will it take?
I'm not sure, sir.
Perhaps 3 months?
How old are you?
I'm 19 years old, sir!
19?
Maybe you're too young to know.
I'll explain.
Attention!
20 years ago,
3 million people died!
They starved to death!
Still, it didn't stop us
from making the nuclear rockets!
They're all ready!
But if you can't break the codes,
it's the same as not having them!
How absurd is that!
The Americans will jump
at the chance to strike.
Three months?
Die now rather than
get killed by Americans!
Cracking the entire system
will take three months,
but we can crack each one
in a week, sir!
I'll give you one day.
Yes, sir.
Check authentication code.
Victor, Quebec, delta, Sierra,
Golf, Kilo, Five, One, Three, Niner.
Authentication code confirmed.
Assign target coordinates.
Target One, Pyongyang.
Target Two, Wonsan.
Target Three, Nampo.
Target Four, Haeju.
A reliable source in the
South Korean government tells us
that the nation's top neurosurgeons have
been appointed to the North Korean leader
who is scheduled for surgery once
his condition improves.
China is fuming!
The nuclear bombers are coming.
They want to declaration retracted now.
It'll be announced soon.
The watch...
Now, we know where it is.
Get it.
May I see some ID, please?
Security service.
Open the gates!
Attention!
Sir!
At ease!
The Supreme Command retracts
PARK Gwang-dong's declaration of war
and suggests talks
with the Republic of Korea to...
The president called for you, sir.
Their troops and mobile missile
launchers have, in fact,
shown an increase in activity
following the retraction.
We firmly believe that this is a standard
North Korean diversionary tactic.
While seeming to open
themselves to negotiations,
they're secretly mobilizing
their forces for military action.
What's that?
Is that... That sounds like gun fire.
Is that gun fire?
We're under attack.
Please stay in the bunker
until the situation is over.
Team 1 and 2
to the Blue House now!
Yes, sir!
The Blue House was attacked?
By who? How?
Don't know?
It's a decoy.
They'll attack here!
Get started.
Stop! Stop!
- What is it?
- It's an emergency!
You can't go in
without permission.
He's injured badly.
He could die!
- Go check.
- Yes, sir.
Rooftop, clear.
Front gate, clear.
Move in.
Grenade!
Flash!
Bring the bodies!
Freeze!
Drop the gun!
Hurry! Get going!
- Go finish the surgery.
- Yes, sir.
This way!
National Security!
He's with us!
Are you okay?
Where's our Leader?
Safely headed to another hospital.
Sit down.
This means they'll start the war
no matter what.
I'll be the bait.
I'll go meet LEE Tae-Han.
Put a tracker on the watch
and give it to me.
Then bomb my location.
Sir! We've accessed
the first one!
Prepare to launch it!
China says they invested in it
for over 20 years, sir.
They're giving it to us at the risk of
exposing their advanced technology.
They say not to forget
their friendship and kindness.
Obviously, they're doing it
to humiliate the U.S. through us.
Give me that.
Deliver this.
North Korea and China are brothers
fighting against Japan and the U.S.
We will always remain brothers.
We will never forget this favor.
SKY OVER NORTHERN JAPAN
HEILONGJIANG, CHINA
X-BAND RADAR BASE
A WACS AIRCRAFT OVER EAST SEA
JAPANESE AEGIS-EQUIPPED WARSHIP
AT EAST SEA
The missiles have entered
the East Sea!
They'll give the coordinates!
Change them.
Sir? It's not Daejeon city,
but the middle of the sea.
The Americans fired
nuclear missiles at our republic!
Launch it now!
Sir! Sir!
A missile launch has been detected
in South Pyongan Province.
Projected target?
Target projected at Japan.
Japan!
Yes, sir.
Prepare to intercept!
- Prepared to intercept!
- Fire!
Quiet down!
Get back to work.
Announce the following
on Central TV.
We crushed the wicked U.S. invaders
who tried to annihilate us.
JAPANESE PRIME MINISTER'S RESIDENCE
It proves what can happen
to us without our nuclear weapons.
Our nuclear weapons
are for self-defense.
However, if the U.S. dares try
to attack us again...
Mr. Prime Minister, sir.
Yes, sir.
Japan will be vanished
from the earth.
But why fire at Japan, sir?
The Americans listen to
the Japanese more than us.
Yes, sir.
A North Korean nuclear missile
exploded over the East Sea.
They must've hacked one.
If they hack the next code,
they'll shoot here.
Comrade Kwak!
Say that our Leader has died.
If LEE thinks our Leader is dead,
it'll buy us some time.
Listen to me!
The longer I stay here,
the more dangerous it gets!
No. 1 is dead.
Gotcha.
NO. 1 DIED
- Is No. 1 really dead?
- No.
He's at another hospital
to undergo surgery.
This place is a frenzy.
They requested another strike,
but the U.S. won't do it.
What?
By now, they realize we will launch
a preemptive nuclear strike upon
any hint of an attack.
So they will not dare
to move recklessly.
We need to consider the collective
security of our entire treaty.
Plus they have already retracted
their declaration.
But they launched the missile
after the retraction!
That makes no sense!
Is our alliance worth nothing
compared to yours with Japan?
You better watch
what you are saying.
Instead of insisting we solve
your own problems for you,
would you please try to
perceive the situation
from the point of view
of your allies.
Let's just wait it out.
Do you think we can destroy
all their nuclear weapons?
If we miss even just one...
don't give your consent, sir.
I'll take full responsibility.
No, I give consent.
Let's try everything we can.
Feeling better?
Looking good, pal.
Will you excuse us?
They took out the code generator
and put in the tracker.
It'll work up to 200 meters underground.
It's made of radioactive material.
See this red button?
If you press this,
it changes the signal.
Then we'll know you're there.
It's bad for you.
Give me that.
Thanks for worrying.
Why?
Worried about me
not living long?
No, I don't want
the radiation around me.
Hold on.
- Wear this.
- Forget it.
It's South Korea.
Wanna advertise you're a commie?
Here.
So, Cheol-woo.
What does your name mean?
It means 'strong friendship'.
Your name means
'bright world', right?
Good memory.
I thought you didn't hear me.
Tell me something funny.
I'm not interested.
I gotta lighten up the mood, huh?
Know why my friend
is moving to Seoul?
How would I know?
It's a good Korea move.
What's the name of a place
where chubby people live here?
There's a place like that?
Banpo-dong! (pun for half-fat)
Then, what's the place
where really fat people live?
Gaepo-dong! (big fat)
How did you know?
You were a spy, weren't you!
I should report you
for the reward.
I saw some of your comedy shows.
Why you little...
You warn your girl not to listen
to our music, but you watched shows?
Comrade UHM?
What comrade Kwak?
Make it out alive.
And gain some weight.
I'll lose some.
Then let's live together
in Banpo-dong.
And have drinks sometimes...
What is G-Dragon saying anyway?
I don't know either.
My heart is cod and
there's no one to say.
Sometimes I want to laugh,
but there's no one by me.
Maybe I'm missing you oh oh
Maybe I'm missing you
Here you go.
May I borrow that?
My card?
I can't say I'll pay you back,
but let me use it?
Thank you!
This is the address you gave me.
I'll be going then.
Are you sure
this is the right place?
It looks like it.
I'll wait for you here
just in case.
No, let's just part here.
Damn commie is so cold.
What?
It's not here?
Comrade Cheol-woo.
It's weird hearing my name
from you.
Once this is over,
send the girl back to the North?
Her family will be waiting.
Of course, I will.
You should make peace
with your wife too.
- The doctor seemed really nice.
- I know that.
You forgot your things.
Comrade Cheol-woo.
Yes?
If things end well,
and travel is allowed
between our countries,
please send them
to this address.
The pink one is for my girl.
The blue one is for my wife.
Thanks for everything, Cheol-woo.
My steel-strong pal!
Take care!
Take care...
I'm so sorry.
- Comrade UHM?
- Yes.
Welcome back home.
At present,
LEE Tae-Han has seized control
of North Korea.
We suspect he and his men
are working from a secret bunker.
But we don't know
their exact location.
A North Korean named
UHM Cheol-woo,
who brought No. 1 down from Kaesong
and requested our help,
has gone back up
to meet LEE Tae-Han.
We put a tracking device on him.
His location is being traced live.
Well done, comrade UHM.
The director is waiting for you.
I command
the Republic's most elite troops!
At last, after dozens of years,
the end has come for
the Americans and their allies.
In a few minutes,
our proud nuclear bombs
will explode over South Korea!
Their cherished American weapons
will be turned into scrap metal!
Comrades! Be proud of...
You killed hundreds of our people
by bombing Kaesong!
How can our soldiers
kill our people!
You betrayed me?
Why'd you betray our Leader!
Who betrayed who!
He executed over 100 generals
in our military!
We're the ones
who were betrayed!
We built this country
and protected it all these years!
We made countless opportunities
to liberate South Korea!
We even made nuclear weapons,
but he won't use them!
A friend I met in the South
said this!
Rather than division itself,
people of a divided nation
suffer more from those
who take advantage of it!
I witnessed that suffering
in Kaesong!
I can't let the entire country
suffer too!
A bomb will strike here!
Get out!
I request the order to strike.
Take care...
everyone.
My beloved citizens,
I believe there should never be
a war on this land ever again.
I will actively seek peace talks
with North Korea.
INTER-KOREAN TRANSIT OFFICE
A divided nation
must be united again!
It's the only way to heal the pains
of the last 100 years of our land!
It will also contribute
to world peace.
Welcome to the democratic People's
Republic of Korea.
He's waiting inside.
Welcome, Mr. Gwak.
How is our Leader?
He's recovering well.
Then he should return soon.
With guaranteed peace,
I think he'll recover sooner.
May I help you?
You have a guest
from South Korea.
How do you do?
Are you moving away?
Yes, we are being sent to
the embassy in Cuba.
You must be In-young.
Greet him, In-young.
Hello, sir.
I'm your daddy's friend.
We have the same name.
Cheol-woo.
I'm KWAK Cheol-woo.
Here.
These are for you and your mom.
Daddy sent them.
My daddy did?
Yes, he did.
I'm JUNG Se-Yong,
Minister of Unification.
I'm Premier PARK Ki-hyun.
Guaranteed peace?
How can we ensure that?
Give us half of
your nuclear weapons.
It'll guarantee the end of
both Koreas if we go to war.
To avoid that,
let's start on a new era of peace.
We got them, sir.
Repatriate him.