No, I shouldn't interrupt him.
He'll call me.
Director Gold. Did you meet her?
Are you all right?
I told you to sleep. It's late. Why aren't you asleep?
I usually go to bed very late.
My nickname is "night owl".
I thought we promised not to lie to each other.
Are you telling the truth?
Of course, I am.
I called in case you were waiting. Go to bed now.
Director Gold?
Are you okay? Where are you right now?
It's late.
I shouldn't have called.
Good night.
Director Gold. Director Gold?
Deok Mi.
You thought I wouldn't be worried if you hung up like that?
If you want to cry, do it in front of me, so I can comfort you.
What are you doing here alone?
You're making me so upset. I hate you.
Don't smile with that face that's about to cry.
I want to cry.
Because you're hitting me so hard.
Director Gold, are you asleep?
Yes.
Shall we go home?
I don't think I'll be able to sleep if I go home.
It feels so strange.
What does?
The person who I've wondered about my entire life...
is sleeping downstairs right now.
It feels strange.
Then come over to my house.
But how did you know I was here?
You didn't know?
I implanted a GPS device inside your body.
Did I tell you about my parents?
The parents who adopted me?
No, right?
They were nice people.
They adopted a seven-year-old kid and raised him happily.
My parents once told me this.
"Your mother gave birth to you and raised you..."
"because she loved you."
"She had no choice but to let us raise you."
"So you have not been abandoned."
"You're being protected." That's what they said.
But the person I met today...
said she was sorry to me.
So it doesn't feel like I've been protected.
It's like I've been abandoned again.
She probably...
wanted to say those words all her life.
She loved you so much,
and she was sorry she couldn't be with you.
Do you think so?
You should get some sleep.
You'll feel better when you wake up.
(Episode 14: A Star That Shines My Dark Heart)
Secretary Kim, is Hyo Jin actually riding the bus right now?
Yes, she must've learned how to charge her BC.
"BC"?
What's that?
It means she learned how to charge her bus card.
I thought she'd call me crying to take her back.
But she learned how to charge her bus card?
What do you think?
Tell me. What do you think?
The next stop is Jindan...
Oh, my gosh.
Did you sleep well?
What about you?
Director Gold. Ms. Sung.
- Hello. - Hello.
Wouldn't you call this an act of privatizing the art gallery?
You all came to work early.
- We came on time... - Yes, we're early.
I don't think we need to change the sofa.
It's still very cushiony.
- What is wrong with you? - Why would you do that?
Here. Eat this.
We have to see that kind of stuff as we work,
so the least we can do is keep ourselves full.
You're right.
Two iced Americanos.
- Can I get a straw? - Oh, sure. A straw.
- Here you go. Enjoy. - How much is this?
It's 80 cents.
- Let me take your order. - Two iced lattes, please.
Two iced lattes.
I'll take your card. Would you like the receipt?
- No, it's okay. - Okay.
So you're telling me that Seon Joo helped you fix your guitar?
- Yes. - And she went to your show?
- Yes. - And she even made a fan club?
Yes.
- So you think Seon Joo likes... - Hey.
Seung Min.
- What are you asking him? - I was just...
Never mind. What did he ask you?
He wanted to know if you like me.
You're even doubting me now?
- No, that's not it. - Ms. Lee.
Isn't it true that you like me?
What I like is music.
I like your music.
I told you, didn't I? She likes me.
I guess you're right.
What are you talking about?
Seung Min, are you...
(Producer Yoo Joong Hyeok)
- What's this? - My friend's a music producer.
And he's looking for a guy who's in a band.
So I thought about introducing Joo Hyuk to him.
Really?
Why would you do that?
Because you like him.
As a fan.
So I figured you'd get to smile more if Joo Hyuk becomes successful.
Seon Joo.
I feel...
the happiest when you smile.
But I had forgotten that.
From now on,
I'm going to focus on making you smile.
I don't care about variety shows or getting promoted.
I just want to make you smile.
That's all I'm going to focus on from now on.
- So... - But Ms. Lee told me...
that she doesn't want me to become too famous.
She wants to keep me hidden to herself.
- Should I leave you guys alone? - You should've done that earlier.
Seon Joo.
- Seung Min. - Yes?
I'm not forgiving you.
I'm just giving you a second chance.
Okay, that's all I need.
- Honey. - Let me go.
I said I'm only giving you a second chance.
Thank you.
(Cha Shi An)
Hello?
At first,
I thought you approached me because you heard some kind of a rumor.
I also got suspicious thinking that you were after a scandal.
But I was strangely drawn to you.
The more I got to know you, I felt very comfortable around you,
and I wanted to become close to you.
We both liked Lee Sol's paintings, and you also lived right above me.
All of that felt like fate.
But eventually,
I guess I was right all along,
Ryan.
Mr. Cha.
I'll send you my mom's number.
Give her a chance to explain.
It might be an apology or an excuse, but give her a chance to explain.
Just this once.
Ms. Sung, we need to give...
the final confirmation regarding the catalog design by next week...
if we want it printed according to schedule.
How should we introduce Lee Sol's paintings?
Have you gotten any calls?
I asked everyone I know, but I couldn't get anything.
When do we need to confirm it by?
Next Wednesday.
Then let's look a little more.
Okay, I also can't wait to see the final piece.
Okay.
(If anyone knows or owns a similar painting, please contact me.)
Hello? Hi, this is Sung Deok Mi from Cheum Art Gallery.
Right. Thanks for your email.
We're interested in Lee Sol's soap bubble series...
that were sold in the previous auction.
Oh, from the seller?
Yes, two more pieces from the series.
So they're going to place the first sale at the next auction?
- Two pieces? - How many is that in total?
- Eight. - Actually, I was hoping maybe...
you could first sell them to us in private.
Of course, we will pay extra to show our appreciation.
Yes, sure. Please let us know.
Thank you very much. Bye.
How did it go?
The collector who sold the painting last time found two additional ones.
They're going to sell them to us, and they told me that they'll call.
Gosh, that's great!
That means we only need to find one more, right?
Nice!
They're going to send us an image file of the paintings.
- Okay, okay. - We did it.
Knock, knock.
What's the "knock, knock" for when you're already inside?
I have good news for you.
We found two more of Lee Sol's paintings.
Okay.
Director Gold, you know what a picture puzzle is, right?
- Do you want to try that? - What?
Come here.
You know how sometimes there are hidden messages in movies?
These paintings also have hidden messages.
Why don't you try to find them?
Did you find them?
These...
Soap bubbles, a rocking horse,
a Ferris wheel, and the Viking ship ride.
They're the things that children especially enjoy.
I think I know what the artist was thinking...
when she drew these paintings.
You do too, right?
How about you call it an early day?
I'm sure there's someone you should meet.
She'll most certainly be waiting for you.
It's Cheum Gallery, right?
Hello?
This is Ryan Gold.
I see.
I'd like to talk.
Could you spare me some time?
Would you like something to drink?
I don't have any coffee though.
Tea is fine. I can't drink coffee anyway.
Thank you for reaching out to me first.
I missed you.
I know that...
I don't have any right to say that.
However, if I must be shameless to see you,
then that's what I'll be.
I missed you, Yoon Jae.
I don't have any memories.
All I remember about you is how you look from behind.
You're either painting...
or leaving me behind.
Why did you abandon me?
I'm sorry.
Why did you leave me?
I didn't.
I only thought I'd be gone for a while.
I was going to return to you soon.
I didn't expect it to take 26 years.
That day...
I shouldn't have gone there that day.
I was barely getting by when I was suddenly offered a contribution.
With the money,
I thought about cooking you a delicious meal...
and taking you to the amusement park you always wanted to go to.
That's why we went out that day.
Yoon Jae, can you play by yourself for a moment?
I won't be long.
Where are you going?
Someone offered to help me with my paintings,
so I'm going to meet him.
He's quite scary though.
Do you still want to join me?
Have fun in the playground.
I'll be back before you know it.
You'll be back soon, right?
Of course, I will.
I had no idea that it'd be the last time...
we see each other.
On my way back to you,
I got in an accident.
My gosh. Miss?
Are you all right?
I suffered a major injury.
My Yoon Jae...
Then because of that accident...
That accident took everything from me.
I lost my precious boy.
Is this the truth?
Then the orphanage...
I didn't abandon you.
I know this might sound like an excuse,
but when I came to,
a long time had passed.
I searched for you everywhere like a crazy woman...
and asked around for any news of you but couldn't find you.
I never abandoned you, Yoon Jae.
I never wanted to leave you.
I'm sorry.
Leaving you all alone in an unfamiliar place,
my accident,
and not being able to find you...
I apologize for it all.
After I had lost you,
I lived my whole life in regret.
My whole life.
This might all seem like just an excuse to you,
and you can still hate me...
and resent me all you want.
Just like this,
I only ask for your permission to let me see you from afar.
Yoon Jae.
I...
have somewhere to be. I'm sorry.
Why did you come back?
Can I stay like this for a while?
Did you see her?
Can I ask what you two talked about?
Words I want to believe...
that can't possibly be true.
She didn't abandon me. Apparently, she lost me.
Then what about...
your memories at the orphanage?
I have no idea. The version I know is completely different.
I couldn't resent her...
nor understand her.
You were a little boy back then, so your memory could be wrong.
Instead of focusing on memories, let's feel her sincerity.
I'd like to do that too.
You're my friend whom I spent my entire life with.
It was nice to see you again.
Pictures don't lie.
(Jerk Eun Gi)
Hey.
Deok Mi, come out for a second.
What?
I'm in front of your house. It'll just take a second.
Why is he here?
You might faint and die if you run hard like that at night.
There's something I really wanted to say.
What is it?
Happy birthday. It's your birthday soon.
But why are you empty-handed?
I have a birthday gift too.
- Me. - You're so lame.
I've just returned as your friend.
Nam Eun Gi, who has been your best friend for 33 years.
I'm really embarrassed to say this,
but do you remember...
when I ran away from home because I didn't want to be an athlete?
Do you remember grabbing me by my hair and dragging me home?
I can't believe you still remember that.
I said you were nothing to me that time,
and you beat me up so much.
You told me not to say that to family.
Of course.
It hurt so much that I wanted to cry, but I couldn't help but smile.
When you said I was your family.
I felt so grateful.
I felt that I should...
stay like that with you without changing for a long time.
But...
I started to like you.
That's the truth.
But I realized something while we spent time apart.
I just...
like it when you smile.
Even if I'm not the person beside you.
Even if you're a fangirl, or there's another man beside you.
As long as you're happy, and you're smiling,
that's what makes me happiest.
You can call that a family, right?
My friend, who is so brave and has a really beautiful smile,
Sung Deok Mi.
I'm sorry for making you feel uncomfortable all this time.
I'm really sorry.
Will you accept me as your friend now?
Eun Gi.
Thank you for saying that.
And thank you for coming back.
You still have to give me a birthday gift.
I brought you one. Me.
What would I use you for?
A tiger is stronger than a lion.
Are you mad? I'll bring the Lion here.
- Bring him. - Are you sure?
- I'll shoulder throw him. - Don't be ridiculous.
What do you think? Looking at a man working from behind.
Do I look cool?
You look very cool.
Shi An, I have...
a lot to tell you.
By any chance, did Ryan call you?
How do you think he knew your number?
I know.
I've always known for a long time.
That you had a very painful past...
and that I have an older brother.
But why didn't you tell me?
Since it was such a hurtful memory to you.
So I waited.
Until I grew old enough for you to tell me...
and rely on me.
I thought you were still a baby.
Thank you, Shi An.
Did it go well with Ryan?
I guess it didn't go well.
I did something unforgivable.
Mom.
- Yes. - Let's show him...
all of your paintings.
That doesn't sound like a good idea.
Why?
All of this happened...
because of those paintings.
It's so cruel.
Ryan is the person who must see those paintings more than anyone.
He must see them.
For his own sake as well.
Mom, wait here for a second.
Yes, Mr. Cha. I was just about to call you.
We found two more of Lee Sol's paintings.
We expressed our interest in purchasing them.
I'll call you again once we receive an answer.
Okay. Then is there just one piece left now?
Yes. We're trying our best to find it, so...
There's no need.
- Why? - I know who has...
the last painting.
I really hope Ryan will see that last piece.
Can you persuade him?
At this late hour?
And she's even walking...
such a far distance? My daughter Hyo Jin?
Mr. Kim, check how safe this neighborhood is.
Mom!
Mom, did you go grocery shopping?
Just some ingredients for japchae and some squid.
Do you like squid soup?
Yes. I love everything that you cook.
Let's go.
- Mr. Kim? - Yes, Ms. Eom.
Did you just hear Hyo Jin call her "mom"?
Yes.
What do you think?
Why are they walking arm in arm? Tell me what you think!
I think she has stolen your daughter from you.
Oh my gosh!
Yes, Deok Mi.
Director Gold, I'll send you an address, so head over here.
- What? - I received a sudden call.
The owner of Lee Sol's painting wants to show it to us.
It's the last remaining piece.
Hurry up, I'll be waiting.
This is where the painting is?
Yes, the owner kept it in the cathedral.
So we agreed to meet here.
You're here.
Deok Mi.
- To be honest... - She did nothing wrong.
I'm the one who asked her to bring you here.
My mom also didn't know...
that you were coming.
I'm sorry you didn't know.
You can go back...
if this is making you feel uncomfortable.
Mom.
Director Gold.
If it's hard to be here as Heo Yoon Jae,
just think that you're here as a museum director.
We need to hold the exhibition.
And in order to do that, we need to look at the painting.
Can you show me...
your last painting?
Ms. Lee Sol.
"Please protect this child."
That's what I prayed for as I decided to keep this here.
You don't remember, do you?
This is Yoon Jae.
Heo Yoon Jae.
Mom.
I'm hungry.
Mom, I'm hungry.
Mom.
- What do you want to eat, Yoon Jae? - Doenjang soup.
- What? - Doenjang soup.
Mom, is this me?
- It's me. - Yes.
We're both...
smiling.
We look very happy.
Mom, look at this!
Mom, did you see that?
It's so pretty.
By the way, are you okay, Mr. Cha?
I'm sure you were also startled.
I might not have been as desperate as my mom,
but I've also been waiting for this day.
We finally found all of my mom's paintings.
And we even found Ryan, the child that my mom lost...
because of her paintings.
By any chance, are you a saint from the skies?
People often ask me that.
It's all thanks to you. Thank you.
It was nothing.
Ms. Lee, I'd like to officially introduce myself to you.
I'm Sung Deok Mi, the senior curator of Cheum Gallery.
What brings you here at this hour?
I heard you know where the last painting is.
I don't want my paintings to go public...
Will you take a look at this first?
(Cheum Gallery 5th Anniversary Celebrity Collection Exhibition)
If people only see bits and pieces of your series,
they'll all come up with different interpretations.
But if we also exhibit the last piece,
everyone who sees the paintings will be able to realize...
the true meaning behind these paintings.
Your ardent affection toward a certain child.
I really want to show that to Director Gold.
Not just as a curator,
but also for the happiness of the man I cherish.
You must like him very much.
It's not just because of that.
I really want to hold...
your official debut as an artist at Cheum Gallery.
Please give us your approval.
By the way, I've been wondering if I should ask you this or not.
What is it?
- No, never mind. - What is it? You can ask me.
By any chance, are you my fan?
Your fan?
- I like you, so I guess I am. - Right?
Yes, I like your band's music.
Thank you.
We're going to release a new song soon.
What's the genre?
- It's going to be hip-hop... - Yes?
mixed with a little bit of acoustic...
You finally saw every single one of Lee Sol's paintings.
How did it feel?
I realized something once I saw the painting.
She loved me...
and protected me.
I was a boy who was loved.
Then feel more of that love. I'll let your mother have you today.
Go on.
Ms. Sung, the Chinese art dealer just called.
The seller agreed to sell Lee Sol's paintings.
Really?
We'll be able to put all nine paintings on display then.
Did you locate the last one?
Shipping will begin next week.
Ms. Sung, Ms. Yu, we did it!
The merchandise is 99 percent ready too.
I just need to put them on display now.
The exhibition will be held soon, so let's keep up the good work.
Sure thing!
Why didn't you tell me that moving artwork was this tiresome?
I forgot how exhausting it can be.
I wonder why we always forget.
It makes us do it again next time.
I know we're busy with the exhibition,
but shouldn't we be treated to a nice team dinner?
I am no longer in possession of my mom's credit card.
Maybe Ms. Sung's boyfriend can pick up the bill.
My boyfriend?
I'll cash in one of my coupons then.
Get changed, guys.
Nice!
So these are the only places that I'm allowed to use?
That's not what we talked about.
Additional pieces will be put on display...
and everyone wants a decent amount of space.
I'd appreciate your understanding.
- Hello, Ms. Choi. - Hello.
If you're not done here, I can always come back.
We're done.
Aren't we?
You say we are, so what choice do I have?
I have plans with a friend anyway.
A friend? You have one in Korea?
Yes, thanks to Ms. Sung.
I'll get going then.
Good luck, guys.
Thanks to me?
So what are you here for?
You have to pay up today.
The staff members are exhausted from managing all the preparations.
A team dinner would boost our spirits.
Fine. How about that makgeolli place we went to?
No way.
- Why not? - You're really heavy.
But I won't get drunk today.
As if.
"As if?"
Why do two perfectly nice words sound sarcastic?
Study up on your Korean and you'll know.
Here's your iced Americano.
Joo Hyuk, is it true that you're releasing an album?
I'll sign it for you when it's released.
You're what I call a successful fanatic.
You went from his fan to his sponsor.
It's crucial for fangirls to have a keen eye.
I took time off from it all, but my taste is still there.
It's why you married Seung Min...
Hey! Are you speaking ill of him?
- I thought you two were fighting. - He's mine to bad-mouth.
Hi.
Hello.
Who are you?
I was here before.
No, you're meeting her for the first time.
Why did you want to see me?
I'll be too busy once the exhibition starts,
so we should get drinks before it begins.
- On one condition. - No hopping bars.
Can I use the restroom first?
- Hi, Deok Mi. - Seon Joo, hi.
I'll have to take a rain check.
A team dinner came up.
All my friends have plans this evening.
Eun Gi has plans?
Apparently, he has a new friend.
She's not a friend.
- A new friend? - Yes.
They seemed close.
She's not a friend!
What will you be having tonight?
It'll probably be makgeolli.
It's Heo Yoon Jae's favorite.
Heo Yoon Jae?
It's Director Gold's Korean name.
Even his name is pretty.
I'll see you tomorrow then.
It's really hard to see her these days.
Seon Joo.
Who's Heo Yoon Jae?
Why did Deok Mi mention that name?
It's Director Gold's Korean name.
Director Ryan Gold?
Yes, he must've figured out what he was called before his adoption.
Let's go and get that drink.
I'm afraid I'll have to decline.
- Maybe next time. - There will be no next time.
Like I said, I'll be too busy.
We'll go for extra rounds next time. I'm sorry, but I have to go.
Bye, Seon Joo.
Bye.
If it's all right with you, we could drink together.
I'm good.
It'll probably be uncomfortable.
Right.
- Mom. - Yes?
You know...
What is it?
Well...
That boy...
That boy?
Yes.
What was his name again?
Why are you bringing him up?
It's nothing, guys. Let's just eat.
I don't know what came over me.
Go on and eat.
Here you go.
For the special exhibition...
Hold on a second. Isn't it Ms. Sung's birthday tomorrow?
It probably is.
We'll celebrate it as a group today,
and you two can enjoy the day alone together tomorrow.
What about the birthday cake though?
(Place an order)
I'm ordering it right now. It'll be here soon.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- Happy birthday to you - Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday, dear Ms. Sung - Happy birthday, dear Ms. Sung
Thank you, everyone.
The cake is really good.
Cheers!
What are you doing?
Are you keeping him on a tight leash?
He won't drink a single drop of alcohol today.
- I'm going to. - You can't.
Are you taking herbal medicine?
- No. - Then why not?
He has something to do tonight.
As in what?
There's something we're going to do together.
That's TMI for sure.
So, are you two really going to date or not?
What? Who do you mean? Us?
My goodness. That is absolutely never going to happen.
You never know what might happen in life. How could you be so sure?
Hey.
We should at least know that nothing will happen between us.
- What are you doing? - You should know how I feel too.
Come on, please don't date!
I can barely stand looking at these two dating.
If you two date too, it'll be so annoying.
- Okay. - Calm down.
Enjoy a second round.
Director Gold, can't we go for a third round too?
Knock yourself out.
Thank you so much.
- Let's go. - Good night.
Have fun.
What are we doing tonight?
You didn't even let me drink.
First of all, change into something comfortable. I'll wait.
(Heo Yoon Jae)
Deok Mi?
Director Gold.
Deok Mi, what is this?
It's my birthday tomorrow.
I want to receive a birthday gift.
Draw my picture.
You know that...
I can't draw.
You can do it.
You drew my hand last time.
Nothing has changed.
I must remind you...
that my profile is beautiful.
But my neckline is even more gorgeous.
How do I look? Don't you want to start drawing?
You just have to trace the outlines of my face.
It looks pretty.
Artist Ryan Gold.
I love you.
He's it! We need to run!
Come and catch us!
My name is Sung Deok Mi, and I'm seven years old.
What's your name?
My name is Heo Yoon Jae.
(Her Private Life)